Act like an angel and dress like crazy
All the girls are girling girling
All the girly girls
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da
Act like an angel and dress like crazy
Ya descend in my heart
Ya 私の心臓に降臨
Ya 내 심장에 강림
Ya, el advenimiento en mi corazón
Ya 降临在我的心脏
You're like CPR
君はCPRみたいに
넌 CPR같이
Eres como una CPR
你就像CPR
Like Pikachu when I touch
触れれば like ピカチュウ
손대면 like 피카츄
Si te toco, es like Pikachu
触碰时like皮卡丘
One million volt thunderbolt, it’s pumping
100万ボルトの電気 it’s pumping
백만 볼트 전기 it’s pumping
Una electricidad de un millón de voltios it’s pumping
百万伏的电力 it's pumping
I'm an otaku bestie
Go crazy, that candy's sassy
クレイジーに that candy's sassy
미쳐 that candy's sassy
Qué locura that candy's sassy
疯狂 that candy's sassy
Renewed the neuronal system
ニューロンシステムを更新
뉴런의 체계를 갱신
Renuevo el sistema nervioso
更新神经元的体系
Broke out of the prison in my head
脳内の監獄 脱獄したの
내 머릿속 감옥 탈옥했지
Escapé de la prisión en mi cabeza
从我脑海中的牢笼越狱
Galileo
ガリレオ
갈릴레오
Galileo
伽利略
I put myself on trial, every day
自ら審判する 毎日
스스로 심판해 매일
Me juzgo a mí mismo cada día
每天都自我审判
In my brain
脳内では
뇌속에선
En el cerebro
在脑海中
I was told to go moderately crazy
適度にクレイジーにって言ったよね
적당히 미치라 했지
Me dijeron que no enloqueciera demasiado
要适当地疯狂
Why can’t you stop?
I don't know the 6 W's, dammit
知らない 5W1Hなんてクソ食らえ
몰라 육하원칙 따윈 제길
No conozco las seis W, mierda
去他的什么六何原则
I'm that material
私ってそういうふうにできてる
난 그런 재질
Estoy hecha de ese material
我就是这种风格
My answer is make me super CRAZY
私の答えは make me super CRAZY
내 답은 make me super CRAZY
Mi respuesta es make me super CRAZY
我的回答是 make me super CRAZY
Crazy crazy crazy crazy
Act like an angel and dress like crazy
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da
Da da da da da
All the girls are girling girling
All the girly girls
Back in the days, the me that fell short of crazy
Back in the days 本物の「クレイジー」になれなかった me
Back in the days 미침에 미치지 못했던 me
Back in the days, no podía enloquecer en la locura, me
Back in the days 原本不够疯狂的me
I will no longer bear false witness before my attraction
もう 惹かれる思いに嘘の証言はしない
더이상 내 끌림 앞에 거짓 증언은 않지
Ya no doy un testimonio falso sobre mi atracción
不要继续在我的吸引力面前作伪证
What it means, what it's worth, what it can and can't do
どんな意味 どんな価値 可能と不可能
무슨 의미 또 무슨 가치 가능과 불가능
¿Qué significado tiene? ¿Qué valor tiene? ¿Qué es posible o imposible?
什么意义 什么价值 可能与不可能
Hush now
もう全部 shhh
이젠 다 쉿
Ahora, todos hagan shh
现在全都嘘
Yeah me and my girls
We know we will go blind, but we still give the sun a kiss
目が眩むと分かってても あの太陽に kiss
우린 눈이 멀 것을 알아도 저 태양에 kiss
Kiss al sol, aun sabiendo que nos cegará
明知会闪瞎我们的眼睛 也要对那太阳kiss
Galileo
ガリレオ
갈릴레오
Galileo
伽利略
I put myself on trial, every day
自ら審判する 毎日
스스로 심판해 매일
Me juzgo a mí mismo cada día
每天都自我审判
In my brain
脳内では
뇌속에선
En el cerebro
在脑海中
I was told to go moderately crazy
適度にクレイジーにって言ったよね
적당히 미치라 했지
Me dijeron que no enloqueciera demasiado
要适当地疯狂
Why can't you stop?
I don't know the 6 W's, dammit
知らない 5W1Hなんてクソ食らえ
몰라 육하원칙 따윈 제길
No conozco las seis W, mierda
去他的什么六何原则
I'm that material
私ってそういうふうにできてる
난 그런 재질
Estoy hecha de ese material
我就是这种风格
My answer is make me super CRAZY
私の答えは make me super CRAZY
내 답은 make me super CRAZY
Mi respuesta es make me super CRAZY
我的回答是 make me super CRAZY
Act like an angel and dress like crazy
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da
Da da da da da
All the girls are girling girling
All the girly girls